Okay, next we have build and within build we have agents.
So agents within Amazon Bedrock service is a managed multi agent framework that allows
you to build agentic A application on AWS.
So you can see some of the agentic A application I have built using this framework.
Next we have flows.
So you can see here flows connect Amazon Bedrock prompts agent knowledge based guardrails
and other AWS services to create test and deploy user defined genetic A workflows.
So if you're looking to create generative AI workflows then you can use Amazon Bedrock
flows.
So let me just quickly show you let me just click on this create flow.
So with just drag and drop you can build generative AI workflows.
So it's a kind of a low code no code solution through which you can build generative
AI workflows with drag and drop.
Then we have knowledge bases.
So knowledge bases are managed retrieval augmented generation or rag solution from AWS.
And we have a dedicated section on rag which is a very important topic.
But for now let's just quickly understand what rag means.
Let's say you have built a generative AI application for your employees.
Let's say they can ask questions related to the company policy.
And the data source you have at the back end could be PDF files, documents and so on.
So using the better knowledge bases quickly with some clicks you can build such a application.
Next we have automated reasoning.
So one of the biggest challenges in generative AI application is hallucination.
And what hallucination means is that in some scenarios your large language model if it doesn't
find the answer in your data source it can generate factually inaccurate answers.
And to prevent that you can use automated reasoning.
Now let's go to the next one we have guardrails.
So guardrails allow you to be compliant with responsible AI policies of your organization.
So we're going to deep dive into responsible AI and guardrails a little later.
But to just help you understand right now let's say you are an investment banking firm
and you build a chat board using the large language model.
Maybe you want to avoid your generative AI application giving investment advice to the customers.
So you can use Amazon better guardrails to block certain topics, keywords, PI reduction.
Okay, next we have the prompt management.
So there are two kinds of prompts you can send to a large language model.
One is the user input or the user prompt and then the second one is the system prompt.
And system prompt provides more context along with the user prompt to generate better response
to the end user quail.
So you can use the prompt management service to create reusable system prompts and store it
here and use it across your generative AI applications within the organization.
Then we have data automation.
So better data automation enables you to automate the generation of valuable insights
from unstructured multimodal content such as documents, images, videos and audio to build
generative AI applications.
So one of the most common use cases across enterprises intelligent document processing.
So let's say you are an insurance company and you get a lot of claim forms.
So right now most organization would do is once they get a scanned claim form, they will
manually do the data entry and through bedrock data automation, one of the use cases.
So once you have the scanned claim form, you can extract the data using bedrock automation
which uses a large language model behind the scenes and then persist in a database automatically.
So that's how you can use bedrock data automation, but you can also use it for media analysis
audio analysis and so on.
Then we have the bedrock agent core.
So bedrock agent core is a relatively new service from AWS.
Now let's say you have built an agent decay application using some of the open source frameworks
like crew AI, land graph and so on.
So once you have built that application, you can use Amazon bedrock agent core to deploy
those applications on AWS.
So it provides a lot of inbuilt capabilities such as memory, built into gateway, identity,
policy, runtime and observability.
And we're going to deep dive into this a little later.
Then we have SS and within SS, we have evaluations.
So evaluations allow us to evaluate the output of the large language model across different
parameters such as accuracy, toxicity and some other metrics.
So it works in two ways either you can do an automatic evaluation which will be done by
another large language model that will evaluate the output of the model that you have selected
or you can also have humans who can evaluate the output of the large language model.
So you can do it for models as well as rag based applications.
And then finally we have the configure and learn.
So we have settings here in the settings what you can do is you can allow model invocation
logging.
So the prompt that you have sent to the model, the response you have got model ID, etc.
All those logs can be sent to either S3, CloudWatch or both.
And all you have to do is enable this model invocation logging here.
The next we have model access.
So this page has been retired till recently you had to request access to the model you
are planning to use but now by default Amazon bedrock allows you access to all the models.
And then we have the user guide.
So there's some documentation from AWS which can help you build generative applications.
And then finally we have the bedrock service terms.
So these are the AWS service terms that you agree to when you use the Amazon bedrock
service.
The reasons they have it here and not for other AWS services is there are some aspects
of legal liability involved especially on the infringement, copyright and so on.
So that's why they have this AWS service terms.
Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture.
Thank you.